{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349804368","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349804368"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_200947"," gameId":" b42d8201-9581-451f-8f4e-8ba9a1b3bc49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-u-e"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349808505","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349808505"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_200947"," gameId":" b42d8201-9581-451f-8f4e-8ba9a1b3bc49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_o-i-e"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349813726","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349813726"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_200947"," gameId":" b42d8201-9581-451f-8f4e-8ba9a1b3bc49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_u-i-e"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349818365","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349818365"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_200947"," gameId":" b42d8201-9581-451f-8f4e-8ba9a1b3bc49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_o-i-e"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349821865","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349821865"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_200947"," gameId":" b42d8201-9581-451f-8f4e-8ba9a1b3bc49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_a-o-u"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349827615","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349827614"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_200947"," gameId":" b42d8201-9581-451f-8f4e-8ba9a1b3bc49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_u_a-o-u"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349840445","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349840444"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_200947"," gameId":" 353c2a7f-7106-4533-b0db-1a9f6d309932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349840678","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349840677"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_200947"," gameId":" 353c2a7f-7106-4533-b0db-1a9f6d309932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349841654","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349841653"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_200947"," gameId":" 353c2a7f-7106-4533-b0db-1a9f6d309932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349842940","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349842940"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_200947"," gameId":" 353c2a7f-7106-4533-b0db-1a9f6d309932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349845843","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349845842"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_200947"," gameId":" 353c2a7f-7106-4533-b0db-1a9f6d309932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349846699","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349846699"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_200947"," gameId":" 353c2a7f-7106-4533-b0db-1a9f6d309932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349847022","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349847022"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_200947"," gameId":" 353c2a7f-7106-4533-b0db-1a9f6d309932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349848268","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349848268"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_200947"," gameId":" 353c2a7f-7106-4533-b0db-1a9f6d309932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349851854","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349851854"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_200947"," gameId":" 353c2a7f-7106-4533-b0db-1a9f6d309932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349852850","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349852849"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_200947"," gameId":" 353c2a7f-7106-4533-b0db-1a9f6d309932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349853111","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349853111"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_200947"," gameId":" 353c2a7f-7106-4533-b0db-1a9f6d309932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349854066","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349854065"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_200947"," gameId":" 353c2a7f-7106-4533-b0db-1a9f6d309932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349856937","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349856936"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_200947"," gameId":" 353c2a7f-7106-4533-b0db-1a9f6d309932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349857984","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349857983"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_200947"," gameId":" 353c2a7f-7106-4533-b0db-1a9f6d309932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349858466","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349858466"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_200947"," gameId":" 353c2a7f-7106-4533-b0db-1a9f6d309932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349862984","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349862983"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_200947"," gameId":" 353c2a7f-7106-4533-b0db-1a9f6d309932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349863057","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349863057"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_200947"," gameId":" 353c2a7f-7106-4533-b0db-1a9f6d309932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349871903","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349871903"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_200947"," gameId":" 353c2a7f-7106-4533-b0db-1a9f6d309932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349878305","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349878305"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_200947"," gameId":" 353c2a7f-7106-4533-b0db-1a9f6d309932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349883586","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349883585"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_200947"," gameId":" 353c2a7f-7106-4533-b0db-1a9f6d309932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349937607","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349937607"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_200947"," gameId":" 6f962eeb-1146-404d-b626-1cba941d7fb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349958502","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349958502"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_200947"," gameId":" 6f962eeb-1146-404d-b626-1cba941d7fb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349975869","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349975869"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_200947"," gameId":" 6f962eeb-1146-404d-b626-1cba941d7fb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349995524","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349995523"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_200947"," gameId":" 6f962eeb-1146-404d-b626-1cba941d7fb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350014107","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350014107"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_200947"," gameId":" 6f962eeb-1146-404d-b626-1cba941d7fb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350031441","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350031441"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_200947"," gameId":" 6f962eeb-1146-404d-b626-1cba941d7fb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_11"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350051019","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350051019"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_200947"," gameId":" 6f962eeb-1146-404d-b626-1cba941d7fb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_13"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350072521","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350072521"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_200947"," gameId":" 6f962eeb-1146-404d-b626-1cba941d7fb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" page_13"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350072587","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350072587"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_200947"," gameId":" 6f962eeb-1146-404d-b626-1cba941d7fb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPINDE"," userResponse":" UPINDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}